[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
ALL PERSONS, LOCATIONS, RELIGIONS, INCIDENTS, AND ORGANIZATIONS IN THIS DRAMA
ARE FICTITIOUS
CHILD ACTORS HAVE FILMED SAFELY UNDER PARENTAL SUPERVISION
SCENES INVOLVING ANIMALS WERE FILMED SAFELY WITH EXPERT ADVICE AND COOPERATION
I just found it stuck between the seats.
So the last place she got off at was Seocho Sejong Tower?
That's right. I think it was a little past 10:00.
The lady was so drunk, so I remember it clearly.
Okay, thank you.
FRIENDLY RIDES MEMORABLE EXITS
25TH: CAN YOU SEND AN EXTRA MILLION WON JUST THIS MONTH?
Did you unlock it? Who was the last caller?
I did.
NAMGUNG-TUSH
TIN CAN BASTARD
You're awake.
What?
Why am I here?
Answer the phone first.
I think it's your boyfriend.
DIRECTOR LEE MI-DO
I guessed right.
It is your boyfriend.
What now?
If you want, I can decline--
Hey, Namgung.
Where are you?
I'll go home. We'll talk there.
-Where are you? I'll pick you up. -Is it her?
-Where is she? Who is she with? -Hold on.
I'll explain at home. I'll be there in 30 minutes.
Hello? Mi-do--
She's coming home.
Explain what happened.
You don't remember?
Wow.
I guess you really don't remember.
Still nothing?
Are you going to meet with Mr. Seo and self-destruct?
Ugh, seriously.
What are you going to do there?
Director Lee.
Wait.
VACANT
Damn it.
ELEVATOR UNDER MAINTENANCE
Please check.
Repairs are complete.
Understood.
I'm very lucky.
What are the odds
of the elevator breaking down right at that moment?
For the record, I didn't do it.
Even I couldn't have predicted a variable like that.
DIRECTOR LEE MI-DO SEND FILE
What are you doing?
Securing evidence for a false accusation claim.
I'll send the settlement agreement by courier today.
Congratulations. You won.
There are no hallway cameras on this floor.
Take the stairs, not the elevator.
And avoid the lobby. Go to the third basement level.
There's an elevator to the next building.
Why?
Because Seo Ju-hyeok can't find out that I was here?
Fine.
I'll take the stairs to the third basement level.
When you send the settlement,
have an expert provide proof
that the files were deleted from your cloud and hard drives.
I will. Get out of my way.
Hey!
What?
What else is there? Just say it!
Once you leave,
will we never see each other again?
5. ARE THERE ANY UNTOLD STORIES BETWEEN US?
Look, this is the office,
and this is the sofa I slept on.
And he just sat there and did work.
I swear. Absolutely nothing happened.
I'm sorry I worried you.
I was so stressed about the settlement agreement.
I was drunk and wasn't thinking.
I think he tried to trick me
into signing the settlement while I was drunk.
What?
You know that lawyer?
That bastard is like a tin can.
Trash that'll take at least 200 years to rot.
What do you mean? Be clear.
But technically, I did start it.
I found out his weakness by accident
and blackmailed him to change the contract in my favor.
Of course,
I really regret it now.
I'm really reflecting on what I did.
Hey!
Give me his number.
Hey.
Should I ask Oh Yeon-ju?
I'm telling you, nothing happened.
After sending the settlement today,
I'll never have to see him again.
So you expect me to let it go?
Then what should I do?
Walk into the law firm holding your hand like a preschooler?
That's what you say after making me worry?
I'm acting like this because I'm sorry.
The guilt is killing me.
You don't even look sorry.
Then what should I do? Huh?
Should I just cry?
Yes, cry! Go on!
Ugh, seriously.
Damn it.
I'm sorry for worrying you, sweetie.
But as you saw in the video earlier,
nothing really happened, sweetie.
I know. That's not the point, sweetie.
Don't force yourself to settle, sweetie.
No, I also just wanted to end it here, sweetie.
I guess it's for the best, sweetie.
Just like that, sweetie?
Why? We'll go to trial if you want, sweetie.
Oh no, sweetie.
I could be writing instead, sweetie.
Alcohol is what caused all of this, sweetie.
I'm taking
a three-month break from drinking, sweetie.
Only three months, sweetie?
It's not just any three months, sweetie.
It includes Christmas, the end of the year,
and the New Year, sweetie.
I'm saying I'll give all that up, sweetie.
Oh, that's huge for sure, sweetie.
I said I'm sorry, sweetie.
-Stop, I get it. -I'm trying here.
Namgung.
Did you wait long yesterday?
No.
Sorry.
Let's meet on the second snowfall this year instead of the first.
I'll be waiting for you.
Mi-do.
I was wondering.
Have you…
25TH: CAN YOU SEND AN EXTRA MILLION WON JUST THIS MONTH?
Never mind. Let's talk after work.
Bambi!
Bambi.
Where did she go?
Bambi!
Hey, move.
Okay.
LOVE EAT
Come on.
City Hall raided us recently,
so she's gotten more cautious.
Oh, no wonder.
By the way, how do you know Bambi?
It's not Bambi. It's Pudgy.
Plenty of people feed her besides us.
Look how chubby she is.
Did you know I was feeding Bambi?
I said it's not Bambi. It's Pudgy.
Pudgy?
Such tragic naming skills.
The mom wasn't caught, right?
Oh, she ran away.
I saw her.
She hasn't returned.
She's not very motherly.
By the way,
why did you go to the Cheonan factory this morning?
That wasn't in the schedule.
I went to explain the new seasoning mix.
It's not what you think, so don't get ahead of yourself.
Why don't you take another shot at becoming a reporter?
That was your dream.
You clearly got rejected,
and now you're trying to fulfill your potential here.
Give it another try. You're still young.
I never even applied.
So I never got rejected.
I specifically aimed for Hunmin Confectionery,
and I was capable enough to get hired that same year.
Wasn't your dream to be a reporter?
Well, briefly in high school.
Just for a while.
Come on. You wanted to be Korea's Amanpour
and recited "A Night Counting Stars" all day in the pavilion.
I memorized that whole poem because of you.
When did I ever do that? I did no such thing.
Let's go in.
How are you holding up? How's the injury?
Oh, I'm fine.
Jeez.
Get it checked out.
Okay.
Back off. We're near work. People will talk.
-Hurry. -Oh, right.
Three steps.
Three steps?
-More, more. -More?
That's good.
Gosh, seriously. I play along, and you cross the line.
Damn it, seriously.
KO MUN-YEONG LAB
I only have eight minutes.
So don't argue. Just listen.
Are you kidding me?
Then text me. I'm busy too.
I'll cut this month's principal and interest by 10%.
Go on. Tell me.
Thank you.
So…
Use contraception properly!
KO MUN-YEONG CHALLENGE
-Use your socials… -Properly!
-Properly! -Properly!
Properly-ly-ly!
Don't do anything…
…you'll regret!
…you'll regret-ret-ret!
How are you handling the kid?
It would've hit the news if PR hadn't found it so fast.
Then why did you do something you would regret?
It's trending again. The Ko Mun-yeong drunk challenge.
When Sang-su got counseling for this last time,
I thought he and I worked it out, but I guess not.
He should go back to counseling.
Come on, he was just having fun. You're overreacting again.
Overreacting?
Yes, overreacting.
Don't you know Sang-su?
He doesn't think much of it.
It's just a fun trend.
His friends do it, so he just joined in.
3:00 p.m. on the 3rd, 7:00 on the 9th, or 11:00 on the 11th.
Pick a time.
I'm scheduling a parent-child session.
Come on, that's overkill.
Stop reading so much into nothing.
You haven't changed.
You got divorced over "nothing,"
and you still treat everything like it's no big deal.
Ever been slapped with a burger?
In a place full of middle schoolers?
Ever been slapped like that?
I want a burger.
I haven't been able to eat a burger since then.
I'm traumatized.
Is this about Sang-su doing that challenge?
Should I talk to him?
We were coming back from a nice trip
and didn't want to cook at home.
We decided to grab burgers on the way, so we went in.
But just because I didn't grab enough ketchup…
she threw a burger at me and asked for a divorce.
You said things were rocky on the trip.
It's not that I'm not over her.
I'm just genuinely curious.
She didn't leave me even when I failed the civil service exam.
Right.
When you blew the store deposit trading overseas stocks,
she let it slide without a word.
No, there was definitely another reason.
I'm sure of it.
Do you really not know?
How would I know if you don't?
Try calling my baby.
His stomachaches seem to linger this time of year.
Your baby's 30 this year.
You call him.
-What are you doing? -Being clingy.
Hold on.
Stop sending gift cards.
Adult movies…
I don't know anything about them.
24 Hours Is Never Enough, 365 Days Isn't Enough,
Secrets of Hiking,
In-Laws Are Fine.
Do you know any others besides these?
I don't.
Without knowing her pay, how would I know how many film contracts she signed?
Hey!
You didn't, did you?
Dude, if Mi-do finds out
that I told you about the studio, I'm dead.
Hey! Namgung!
Nam--
Director Lee, did you see the posting from Danwol City?
You know your script, My Dear Dictator?
You should submit it.
Danwol City's orchestra is quite famous,
so it's a perfect fit for your work.
Oh, that's a great idea.
You should submit it. Have you revised it at all?
You guys must not be busy.
Is pre-production too easy for you?
Or did Director Gong get more flexible with age?
Filming starts late next year,
so we have some time.
Anyway, I looked at the posting,
and the requirements are practically…
ATTACK ON THE WALKING TRIPOD
Yes, Namgung.
She must have signed with another studio. What do we do?
You worked so hard with that studio to get her contract canceled.
I pitched Danwol City.
I keep telling her to do indie films,
but it's not easy.
Once I find out the new studio,
I'll let you know right away…
Namgung, what do I do?
Director Lee is right here.
Okay, you've got my back--
Hello? Namgung? Namgung!
Since when did Namgung Ho become your boss?
When we met at the police station,
he gave me money for a taxi,
and I gave him my number.
That's how we connected…
Did you pay the studio to cancel my contract?
Yeah.
I paid 10% more than your advance to cancel it.
But it was all for nothing,
because you went and signed another contract.
I know you hate me shooting adult films.
Sorry I didn't tell you about the remaining contract.
But Namgung,
this isn't right.
You crossed the line.
For how long?
-What? -How long…
have you been paying her?
It's been two years, as far as I know.
Because that's when you started directing adult films.
Why didn't you tell me?
Why didn't you tell me and just…
I'm not mad at you.
She must have used me to threaten you.
Saying she'd come find me if you didn't pay her.
It's so obvious
what that woman must have done to you.
I did pay her living expenses.
But it has nothing to do with Hwa-young.
Send me the total by next week.
I'll pay you back.
Hey.
Why would you pay me?
I didn't do it expecting you to pay me.
Take it.
Or I won't be able to look at you.
Why would you ruin your career because of me?
I know better than anyone how much films mean to you.
Why should you have to do that?
Namgung.
Don't be ridiculous.
My pride as a director hasn't been ruined just because I directed a few adult films.
Hey.
I'm Lee Mi-do.
I don't let things like that sway me.
Okay?
I'm too ashamed to look at you.
I could go crazy from how sorry and embarrassed I am.
What's so embarrassing about this?
What's really embarrassing is
ten-year-old you going to camp and peeing his pants after seeing a bat.
Hey!
Jeez.
Namgung.
Even if I went back in time,
I'd still make the same choice.
I don't regret it.
I'm sorry.
I didn't even know.
I said awful things to you,
hurt you,
and lashed out.
I'm sorry.
You are?
If you're that sorry…
you're doing the recycling for a month.
I already do that.
Hmm, then dishes for a month.
I already do that too.
Then let's call it even.
Listen.
Don't you dare use this as an excuse to go see Hwa-young.
Got it?
You didn't, right?
I hired a lawyer.
I'm going to do everything I legally can.
I'm ending this for good.
So I think I need to see her one last time.
Just let me do this once.
I'll go with you.
I don't want you to see me with that woman.
Mi-do.
I'll really end it this time.
Just wait for me.
Okay.
Oh, wait a second.
Here.
What's this?
A voice recorder.
Turn it on when you see her, just in case.
For the record, this isn't illegal.
Namgung.
Only say half.
Only say half of what you want to say to Hwa-young.
Pouring everything out might feel good in the moment,
but you'll hurt more later.
My Mi-do has grown up.
Someone raised me well.
I won't leave you to suffer alone anymore.
I'll protect you.
When revising a script,
some scenes inevitably get deleted for the sake of pacing and length.
MY DEAR DICTATOR VER. 12
The so-called deleted scenes.
Even without these scenes, the story still flows and connects well.
They are unknown only to the audience.
Our lives are also made up by deleted scenes such as these.
The ones we want to hide from others.
DELETED SCENES
The untold stories only I know about.
Hey, Namgung.
It's cold. You bundled up, right?
He's sick in bed. Why would he dress up?
Hey, how sick are you to skip fishing?
Are you faking it?
No, I'm not.
Hey.
Did Yeong-do fight with his ex-wife?
Wow, my baby is so perceptive.
I'll bring you some good food later.
Don't cry about your stomachache.
-Okay. -There you go. Good boy.
See you.
Who leaves early for counseling?
Mom put you up to this again?
Rehearse what we practiced earlier.
"All my friends were doing it, so I did it for fun."
"I didn't think much of it."
Say exactly that in front of Mom and the counselor.
-You promised. -You keep your promise, Dad.
I'm really going to stay up all night and play games.
Don't you dare nag me.
Only for a month, though.
Mom wouldn't get hurt even if she found out anyway.
Do you really not know Mom?
Your mom will die of shock.
If she finds out you filmed that to hurt her feelings,
she'll literally die.
Hey, Driver.
You must have seen it too.
365 Days Isn't Enough.
That was the number-one hit film on IPTV last year…
It's you again?
How many days has it been now?
At the car wash, and as a designated driver…
How long will you keep bothering me?
Until you cancel Director Lee Mi-do's remaining contract.
You're so damn persistent.
What's your relationship with Director Lee Mi-do anyway?
-Are you her boyfriend? -I'm a fan.
Huh?
I'm her number one fan.
Damn, that's beautiful. So damn beautiful.
Don't ever contact me again.
That's what I came here to say.
Medical report, photos of bruises.
Hwa-young.
Don't use things like that to get Namgung's sympathy.
If you contact us one more time,
I won't just sit back.
Mom!
Namgung.
That day, I met the seven-year-old you again.
The seven-year-old you that I couldn't protect.
COURT
I will read the verdict.
As there is no proof that the defendant, Line Intercontinental,
intentionally disregarded
the damage to the component,
and as it is difficult to conclude
that the component caused the vehicle defect,
causality cannot be established.
Therefore, all of the plaintiff's claims are dismissed.
Chairman Ko of Jisang did this, didn't he?
His temper is really something.
Fifty billion won's worth of land is about to vanish.
A busted forehead means he's being nice.
Was it Kim Jeong-hwan?
The whistleblower from Line.
We're looking for him.
There's no departure record, so he should still be in the country.
We won the trial,
but if this guy happens to show up,
we're in trouble.
All of Jisang's internal verification reports have been destroyed,
and the three researchers who testified
were all sent overseas.
The audit logs, transaction history,
and raw packet records were deleted and reformatted,
so there's no need to worry.
Just to be safe, find him as soon as possible.
Understood.
She's so hard to read.
She begged to be back in the director's chair,
and now she refuses?
I know. Now she's refusing.
Why are you so calm?
If the truth about my dad gets out,
don't you know it would affect Ju-hyeok?
Then we'll kill her.
Isn't that the best way to shut her up?
Are you crazy?
Are you out of your mind?
Exactly.
That's how you're supposed to react.
Director Lee Mi-do.
Director Lee Mi-do just walked by.
Did you see her?
A master in Hadong cultivated this ujeon tea.
You mean the foreigner we saw at the tea plantation last time?
That's right.
He's one of the few certified tea masters in the UK.
He's a very important person who gets invited to British royal events.
For the past two years,
he's been handling the tea leaves
from cupping to fermentation.
-No wonder. -So the entire hectare of land we saw
belongs to you?
It's been in my family since my grandfather.
This is my first business venture, so I'm quite worried.
Wow, that's so cool!
No wonder you look so elegant.
You have a certain presence. Don't we all agree?
Can I get a taste too?
Oh my, what brings a young man like you to this place?
He's handsome.
I'm very interested in tea.
The aftertaste is a bit bitter.
That's how ujeon tea is.
It's made from young leaves,
so the scent is light,
but it leaves a slight bitterness.
That's the charm of ujeon tea.
No.
It's because you mixed in cheap powdered sejak tea.
You were probably offered investments with guaranteed principal.
She promised upfront profits
and guaranteed dividends so you wouldn't lose money.
But you know what?
It's a scam.
-What? -What?
Despite her appearance,
she has five fraud convictions.
-Oh my. -No way.
We all have other plans, right?
-Yes, we do. -Oh my goodness.
I'll call you later.
You're still looking beautiful, Mom.
How have you been?
What brings you here?
You acted like you'd kill me if I ever called you.
You know why. It's about Mi-do.
I didn't ask her for it.
She pitied me and helped me out.
That's ridiculous.
Like Mi-do would ever do that.
So what?
You've come to confront me over some cash from your girl?
Confront?
That's a cute way to put it.
Singapore DBJ Private Banking, Catherine Tak.
That's you, right?
Since you have no assets in your name, it took me a while to find out.
I submitted proof to the court
that you used Catherine Tak as your alias for the account.
By now,
it's probably been frozen.
I also got the deposit for this place
and the one for the leased land in Hadong provisionally attached,
so just know that.
Son.
Korean law doesn't recognize debt between parents and children.
We're bound by blood.
The law can't do anything about it.
Don't you know that by now?
Of course I know.
That damn law.
That damn blood tie.
So…
I'll use that blood tie to play God.
Emotional instability,
impaired judgment,
delusional disorder, and nervous breakdown.
How's that?
They're reasons to have you committed. Do you like them?
Because I'm your only legal guardian.
Which means,
I can lock you up in a psych ward whenever I want.
Are you crazy?
Have you lost your mind?
Mom.
You shouldn't have messed with Mi-do.
Detectives will be here soon.
I have one last favor to ask.
Don't make this any uglier.
You can at least do that.
Who are you to ruin this?
I've planned this for years!
Who do you think you are?
You're marrying Mi-do soon, right?
Does she know?
About my private loans?
It's probably…
over 300 million won.
You know how it is.
They don't care about renouncing inheritance or the law.
They'll tear you apart to get paid.
Still, rather than paying it back by yourself,
it'd be better to pay it back together with Mi-do.
Shut your mouth!
Is Mi-do still filming?
When does it come out?
I'll do an interview from prison.
Or maybe not?
If Mi-do makes it big,
would that be better for me?
I'll have to think about it.
You think I'll go down alone?
-I'll drag Mi-do into it. -Stop it.
She sent me money for two years.
I'll go to the police and tell them she's an accomplice.
I'm never going down alone.
Hey!
Let go of my mom!
YEONMUHEON
Let go of my mom right now!
Let go!
Get up.
-Where's the money? -I don't have it!
-Give it! -I don't have it!
-Who the hell are you? -My son.
You crazy bastard!
Damn it.
Get out of my way, you fucker!
Come here! Come here!
Damn it!
Ugh, seriously.
You crazy bastard.
Where did this bitch go?
Ugh, fuck.
Let go! Let me go.
You posted used phones, took the cash, and ghosted 12 times. Is that true?
It's all my fault.
He studies art.
But I don't have the means,
so I couldn't even send him to classes.
But since he's a minor, he'll be released soon, right?
Oh, dear.
Thought you hooked a rich guy and were paying the interest.
What's all this?
My husband's life insurance payout is coming.
I'll pay you then.
That's barely anything, isn't it?
How will you pay me back?
-Huh? -Let go of my mom!
Meet me at the 24-Hour Mediterranean Sauna by 4:00.
A large top and size 32 bottoms.
A casual look that's simple but still dapper.
Keep the top, bottom, and jacket under 100,000 won.
It came out to 114,000 won.
It's hard to get a full outfit for 100,000 won these days.
I hate collars like this. They're uncomfortable.
You knew?
Not from the start.
I caught a glimpse earlier.
You were behind the inflatable tube man.
I didn't do it on purpose.
You suddenly took the day off.
And you suddenly went to the Cheonan factory last time.
Of course, you made your intentions clear.
But I was worried you'd get all righteous and do something on your own.
That would be dangerous, so…
So you followed me from home?
I'm sorry.
Whatever. Keep the change.
Let me buy you a meal.
The pork cutlet here is really good.
I went to middle and high school here, so I know.
It's really good. I'll pay.
Deok-sun.
Do I look like I'm in the mood for pork cutlets?
You saw everything earlier.
Maybe some sikhye instead.
Buy me sikhye. I'm craving it.
HOT CHOCOLATE CHIPS
-Sikhye. -And some eggs?
I'll have ramen.
Park Su-a?
It's been a while. How have you been?
Oh, it's been a while.
Hey, let's keep in touch.
I heard you're at Hunmin.
-I'm at Mugang Planning. -I'm at Jaeu Insurance.
We work close by. How have we never seen each other?
I know, right?
When you have time,
let's grab lunch.
-Oh… -Park Su-a.
I'm her cousin.
-Oh, hello. -Hello.
You coming?
Oh, right. Coming.
I should go.
-Okay. -Bye.
That was them, right?
The ones who stole your gym clothes and kept your textbooks.
How did you know?
Your face gave it away.
Why even respond to them? Just ignore them.
But usually, in a situation like this,
wouldn't you speak up for me?
Stop reading comic books.
Me fighting young girls would just be weird and pathetic.
Yeah, yeah.
Next time that happens,
just repeat these three phrases.
"Why would I?"
"So what?"
"Who cares?"
Got it?
Forget it.
I won't see them again anyway.
Besides, it's all in the past.
Back in high school,
I couldn't go to the cafeteria for three years.
What did they say again?
They said I might have AIDS or something.
They made such a huge fuss.
So I couldn't eat a proper meal
and lived on bread and snacks.
That's how I got by.
That's when I started liking snacks.
And that's also why I joined Hunmin.
-Why tell me this now? -What?
Where are you going?
Oh, I'm sorry!
-Are you okay? -Yes, are you?
Darn it.
I'm so sorry.
Park Su-a still gives zero reaction.
It's no fun teasing her.
I know, right?
Ji Su-yeon was fun.
Yeah, Ji Su-yeon was hilarious. The…
Mugang Planning.
Jaeu Insurance.
-And you? -Oh, me?
BQ Construction.
BQ.
Close to Hunmin Confectionery.
Yes, but why…
From now on,
if you ever come across Park Su-a, don't you dare talk to her. Just walk by.
Don't pretend to be friendly just to insult her.
What do you mean?
You can't do this, even as her cousin.
Did Park Su-a say that we bullied her?
We never did anything like that.
You never did?
Hey.
I asked if you never did.
I'm warning you.
If you ever run into Park Su-a on the street and speak to her,
all three of you
will seriously pay for it.
Mr. Namgung…
Ho!
Stop it. Let's go.
You've been warned.
Don't talk to her.
Wow, this is unbelievable.
Hey, Park Su-a, you should apologize to us.
Why would I?
Did you not hear what your cousin just said?
He completely insulted us.
So what?
He really spooked us. Do you have any idea?
Who cares?
Let's go.
Yeah, I'm chopping them now.
So I put them in all at once?
The onions, carrots… And potatoes?
Oh, okay.
And green onions?
Oh, and…
I'll call you back.
Hey, Director Lee!
Open the door.
Open up!
Open the door! Open up!
Open the door!
Ms. Song, what are you doing?
Why aren't you coming back?
Are you trying to torture me to death?
If you keep bothering me, I just might.
I knew it.
I figured as much.
You're getting revenge on me.
I was out of my mind back then.
I'll keep your secret, Ms. Song.
So don't worry and leave.
Suddenly acting all nice.
Just tell me to get on my knees.
No, you don't need to.
I don't want to see you anymore. Just go.
What do you want?
Is it money?
Just say so. Stop pretending to be nice!
Hey!
If you ever come back here again, I won't let you get away with it.
This is your last warning.
Ugh, Song Hae-na, seriously.
Is she trying to test me or…
Song Hae-na is here, right?
Song Hae-na isn't here.
She just left. You can catch her if you go now.
I only believe things I see with my own eyes.
By the way…
why the sudden formal tone?
I no longer hold the upper hand.
Go tell Song Hae-na
that I will never breathe a word about it.
I'm blocking her number now,
so tell her not to try calling.
Did you block my number too?
No wonder.
I couldn't get through to you.
I thought about using another phone,
but my pride wouldn't let me.
Still…
I lost again.
Do you think I came here to catch Song Hae-na?
I'm not an idiot.
It was so annoying.
I kept thinking about it.
So I came to check.
If I just lost my mind that night,
or if I'm still out of my mind.
Besides the deleted scenes you want to hide from others,
there are other hidden scenes.
The ones that even I want to forget.
The ones I want to tear to pieces.
The ones I want to keep hidden.
The ones they must never know about.
Those kinds of untold stories.
I can't help but think you're hiding something.
What is it that makes you refuse to return as a director
and put me through such hell?
You don't want to direct, do you?
You're scared, aren't you?
I knew it. You're scared.
No, I'm not.
That's not it.
Yes, you are.
You want to run away.
You're scared and terrified.
But you feel bad for your boyfriend,
so you're too ashamed to do it.
Am I wrong?
You're wrong.
Want me to help you escape?
You were desperate enough to go beg Song Hae-na,
but I got in the way and ruined it.
You can say you had the talent but just got unlucky.
You got tangled up with some crazy guy,
and got completely screwed over.
Burying a rookie director before they even start
is incredibly easy for me.
Why would you go that far for me?
What do you want from me?
One thing is for sure.
It's not because of the settlement.
Attorney Han.
Did he leave? I thought he was here.
I'm calling about the report on Jisang.
There's something you need to check.
I'm home. Email it to me.
I'll check and call you back.
I…
kissed this man.
Mi-do cries whenever she sees me these days.
Is she going through menopause?
EXPAT POSITION IN PARIS
Are you getting married, Mr. Namgung? You are, right?
I'll let you quit directing.
Let's have some fun for a bit.
Did Mr. Namgung take out a private loan?
I already died when I was seven,
so I'm living on borrowed time.
Mess with me and see.
I'll show you how crazy I can get.
Subtitle translation by Soya Back